人民就是领袖！
The people are leading
人民是在暴动，两者不能混为一谈
The people are rioting There's a difference
注：1793年，华盛顿发表了《中立宣言》，表明了合众国的立场并警告所有公民不要从事偏袒任何一方的敌对行为，该宣言在美国历史上极具重要意义因为它首次明确地把合众国远离欧洲战事、政治作为了一项国策
老实说，你让理想蒙蔽现实的行为实在令人有点不安！
Frankly, it's a little disquieting you would let your ideals blind you to reality
-汉密尔顿？   -先生
-Hamilton?     -Sir
-请起草中立宣言    -好的，先生
-Draft a statement of neutrality   -Yes, sir
你难道忘记了拉法叶？
Did you forget Lafayette?
-什么？   -你难道毫无羞愧之意？
-What?     -Have you an ounce of regret?
你欠着他们的债笔笔堆积，你日日丰满自己的羽翼
You accumulate debt You accumulate power
但在他们最需要帮助之时，你却忘恩负义
Yet in their hour of need you forget
拉法叶是个聪明人，我相信他会没事
Lafayette's a smart man He'll be fine
更别说我比你更早与他熟识
And before he was your friend He was mine
如果世界上每一场革命我们都要参与
If we try to fight In every revolution in the world
那么革命永无止境，我们该何时停止？
We never stop Where do we draw the line?
-多么的"机智"     -好吧，这我承认确实如此
-So quick-witted     -Alas, I admit it
-巧舌如簧不愧是个律师     -我的被告都无罪得释
-I bet you were quite a lawyer     -My defendants got acquitted